Facilities Management Department fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- General office files, 1963 - 1984; F-11-1; 7.68 m of textual records
  - Science complex phase IV, 1965 - 1980; F-11-1-45; 48 cm of textual records
    - Contract - Cana Construction (50-28), 1978; F-11-1-45-0-46 (Archival box - standard 11-55)
    - Contract Deletions (50-29), 1978; F-11-1-45-0-47 (Archival box - standard 11-55)
  - Ski cabin, 1968 - 1978; F-11-1-46; 2 cm of textual records
    - Ski Cabin - General (84-01), 1968 - 1975; F-11-1-46-0-1 (Archival box - standard 11-34)
    - Ski Cabin - General (72-01), 1976 - 1978; F-11-1-46-0-2 (Archival box - standard 11-59)
  - Tennis courts, 1969 - 1970; F-11-1-47; 1 cm of textual records
    - Tennis Courts - General (88-01), 1969 - 1970; F-11-1-47-0-1 (Archival box - standard 11-34)
  - Trailers, 1967 - 1975; F-11-1-48; 2 cm of textual records
    - Trailers - General (90-01), 1967 - 1975; F-11-1-48-0-1 (Archival box - standard 11-34)
    - SFU Residence Competition (90-01), 1967 - 1968; F-11-1-48-0-2 (Archival box - standard 11-34)
  - University Centre building, 1966 - 1978; F-11-1-49; 10 cm of textual records
    - University Centre #1 General (91-02), 1969 - 1973; F-11-1-49-0-1 (Archival box - standard 11-35)
    - Progress Certificates (UCB #1) (91-04-11), 1971 - 1973; F-11-1-49-0-2 (Archival box - standard 11-35)
    - Design (UCB #1) (91-06), 1970 - 1973; F-11-1-49-0-3 (Archival box - standard 11-35)
    - Contract Docs (UCB #1) (91-08), 1971 - 1973; F-11-1-49-0-4 (Archival box - standard 11-35)
    - Materials Testing (UCB #1) (91-12), 1971 - 1974; F-11-1-49-0-5 (Archival box - standard 11-35)
    - University Centre Building - General (56-01), 1976 - 1978; F-11-1-49-0-6 (Archival box - standard 11-58)
    - Beer Garden (56-02), 1975 - 1978; F-11-1-49-0-7 (Archival box - standard 11-58)
    - UCB Renovations (56-03), 1975 - 1978; F-11-1-49-0-8 (Archival box - standard 11-58)
    - UCB - general (91-01), 1966 - 1973; F-11-1-49-0-9 (Archival box - standard 11-61)
  - Long-range planning - Animal Care, 1969 - 1975; F-11-1-50; 13 cm of textual records
    Animal Care Facility
    - Long Range Planning - French Language Training Centre (140-02), 1974 - 1975; F-11-1-50-0-1 (Archival box - standard 11-35)
    - Long Range Planning - Animal Care Facility (140-03), 1974 - 1975; F-11-1-50-0-2 (Archival box - standard 11-35)
    - Fees (140-03-01), 1975; F-11-1-50-0-3 (Archival box - standard 11-36)
    - Animal Care (140-03-02), 1970 - 1975; F-11-1-50-0-4 (Archival box - standard 11-36)
    - Program (140-03-03), 1969 - 1975; F-11-1-50-0-5 (Archival box - standard 11-36)
    - Schematics (140-03-04), 1975; F-11-1-50-0-6 (Archival box - standard 11-36)
    - Site Survey (140-03-05), 1975; F-11-1-50-0-7 (Archival box - standard 11-36)
    - Working Drawings, 1975; F-11-1-50-0-8 (Archival box - standard 11-36)
    - Tenders Received (140-03-07), 1975; F-11-1-50-0-9 (Archival box - standard 11-36)
    - Site Work Contract (140-03-08), 1975; F-11-1-50-0-10 (Archival box - standard 11-36)
    - Inspections and Testing (140-03-19), 1975; F-11-1-50-0-11 (Archival box - standard 11-36)
    - Long Range Planning - Mathematics (140-04), F-11-1-50-0-12 (Archival box - standard 11-36)
  - Central mall, 1973 - 1978; F-11-1-51; 1 cm of textual records
    Erickson, Arthur; Massey, Geoffrey
    - Roof (Mall) (38-04), 1975 - 1978; F-11-1-51-0-1 (Archival box - standard 11-39)
    - Erickson/Massey Claim (Mall) (38-05), 1973 - 1976; F-11-1-51-0-2 (Archival box - standard 11-39)
  - Health services expansion, 1975 - 1979; F-11-1-52; 13 cm of textual records
    Health Services; Department of Biomedical Physiology and Kinesiology
    - Health Services - General (39-01), 1975 - 1978; F-11-1-52-0-1 (Archival box - standard 11-39)
    - Fees (39-02), 1976 - 1978; F-11-1-52-0-2 (Archival box - standard 11-39)
    - Working Drawings (39-06), 1976 - 1977; F-11-1-52-0-3 (Archival box - standard 11-39)
    - Tenders Received (39-07), 1975 - 1977; F-11-1-52-0-4 (Archival box - standard 11-39)
    - Contract (39-08), 1976 - 1977; F-11-1-52-0-5 (Archival box - standard 11-40)
    - Progress Certificates (39-09), 1977 - 1979; F-11-1-52-0-6 (Archival box - standard 11-40)
    - Plans and Specs (39-10), 1977; F-11-1-52-0-7 (Archival box - standard 11-40)
    - Change Orders and Correspondence Part I (39- 12), 1977 - 1978; F-11-1-52-0-8 (Archival box - standard 11-40)
    - Change Orders and Correspondence Part II (39-12), 1977 - 1978; F-11-1-52-0-9 (Archival box - standard 11-40)
    - Design Changes (39-13), 1976 - 1977; F-11-1-52-0-10 (Archival box - standard 11-40)
    - Minutes of Site Meetings (39-16), 1977; F-11-1-52-0-11 (Archival box - standard 11-40)
    - Mechanical Systems (39-17), 1976 - 1978; F-11-1-52-0-12 (Archival box - standard 11-40)
    - Electrical Systems (39-18), 1976 - 1978; F-11-1-52-0-13 (Archival box - standard 11-40)
    - Inspections and Testing (39-19), 1976 - 1978; F-11-1-52-0-14 (Archival box - standard 11-40)
    - Kinesiology (39-21), 1976 - 1978; F-11-1-52-0-15 (Archival box - standard 11-40)
    - Client/Architect Agreement (39-22), 1976 - 1977; F-11-1-52-0-16 (Archival box - standard 11-40)
    - Substantial Completion (39-23), 1977 - 1978; F-11-1-52-0-17 (Archival box - standard 11-40)
    - Warranties and Guarantees (39-24), 1978 - 1979; F-11-1-52-0-18 (Archival box - standard 11-40)
  - Education complex (CBII, Multi-purpose, MPX), 1968 - 1980; F-11-1-53; 83 cm of textual records
    Department of Archaeology; Department of Languages, Literature and Linguistics
    - Classroom Complex Phase III - General (40- 01), 1968 - 1972; F-11-1-53-0-1 (Archival box - standard 11-40)
    - General (40-01), 1978; F-11-1-53-0-2 (Archival box - standard 11-41)
    - Education Complex (40-01), 1976 - 1978; F-11-1-53-0-3 (Archival box - standard 11-41)
    - Client/Architect Agreement (40-020, 1977 - 1978; F-11-1-53-0-4 (Archival box - standard 11-41)
    - Capital Expenditures (40-04), 1975 - 1979; F-11-1-53-0-5 (Archival box - standard 11-41)
    - Construction Management Services (40-08), 1975 - 1978; F-11-1-53-0-6 (Archival box - standard 11-41)
    - Construction Management Contract (40-08-01), 1975 - 1977; F-11-1-53-0-7 (Archival box - standard 11-41)
    - Plans and Specs (40-09), 1975 - 1977; F-11-1-53-0-8 (Archival box - standard 11-41)
    - Change Order Correspondence (40-10), 1977 - 1978; F-11-1-53-0-9 (Archival box - standard 11-41)
    - Jobsite Instructions (40-10-04), 1977; F-11-1-53-0-10 (Archival box - standard 11-41)
    - Schematic Stage (40-11), F-11-1-53-0-11 (Archival box - standard 11-41)
    - Working Drawings Stage (40-12), F-11-1-53-0-12 (Archival box - standard 11-41)
    - Contract Documents Stage (40-13), 1975 - 1976; F-11-1-53-0-13 (Archival box - standard 11-41)
    - Inspections and Testing (40-14), 1977 - 1978; F-11-1-53-0-14 (Archival box - standard 11-42)
    - Minutes of Site Meetings #2 (40-15-01), 1978; F-11-1-53-0-15 (Archival box - standard 11-42)
    - Construction Progress Report (40-15), 1976 - 1977; F-11-1-53-0-16 (Archival box - standard 11-42)
    - Minutes of Site Meetings #1 Part A (40-15-01), 1977 - 1978; F-11-1-53-0-17 (Archival box - standard 11-42)
    - Minutes of Site Meetings #1 Part B (40-15-01), 1977 - 1978; F-11-1-53-0-18 (Archival box - standard 11-42)
    - Mechanical Systems (40-16), 1975 - 1979; F-11-1-53-0-19 (Archival box - standard 11-42)
    - Electrical Systems (40-17), 1976 - 1979; F-11-1-53-0-20 (Archival box - standard 11-42)
    - Hardware (40-18), 1977; F-11-1-53-0-21 (Archival box - standard 11-42)
    - Archaeology (40-19), 1976 - 1978; F-11-1-53-0-22 (Archival box - standard 11-42)
    - Department of Languages (40-20), 1978; F-11-1-53-0-23 (Archival box - standard 11-43)
    - Ramp (40-21), 1978; F-11-1-53-0-24 (Archival box - standard 11-43)
    - Moves (40-22), 1978; F-11-1-53-0-25 (Archival box - standard 11-43)
    - Deficiencies (40-23), 1978; F-11-1-53-0-26 (Archival box - standard 11-43)
    - Heating, Lighting, Electrical and Ventilation (40-26), 1969 - 1972; F-11-1-53-0-27 (Archival box - standard 11-43)
    - Deficiency Reports (CC) Part A (40-66), 1970 - 1972; F-11-1-53-0-28 (Archival box - standard 11-43)
    - Deficiency Reports (CC) Part B (40-66), 1970 - 1972; F-11-1-53-0-29 (Archival box - standard 11-43)
    - Bulk Excavation and Drainage (40-CB-01), 1975 - 1977; F-11-1-53-0-30 (Archival box - standard 11-43)
    - Elevators (40-CB-02), 1976 - 1979; F-11-1-53-0-31 (Archival box - standard 11-43)
    - Materials Testing (40-CB-03), 1977 - 1980; F-11-1-53-0-32 (Archival box - standard 11-43)
    - Mechanical Work (40-CB-05), 1976 - 1979; F-11-1-53-0-33 (Archival box - standard 11-44)
    - Electrical Services Part A (40-CB-06), 1977 - 1979; F-11-1-53-0-34 (Archival box - standard 11-44)
    - Electrical Services Part B (40-CB-06), 1977 - 1979; F-11-1-53-0-35 (Archival box - standard 11-44)
    - Damproofing (40-CB-07), 1977 - 1979; F-11-1-53-0-36 (Archival box - standard 11-44)
    - Roofing and Waterproofing (40-CB-08), 1977 - 1979; F-11-1-53-0-37 (Archival box - standard 11-44)
    - Supply Hollow Metal Doors and Frames (40-CB-09), 1977 - 1979; F-11-1-53-0-38 (Archival box - standard 11-44)
    - Sand Blasting (40-CB-10), 1977 - 1979; F-11-1-53-0-39 (Archival box - standard 11-45)
    - Glazing Windows and Skylights (40-CB-11), 1977 - 1979; F-11-1-53-0-40 (Archival box - standard 11-45)
    - Finish Hardware (40-CB-12), 1977 - 1979; F-11-1-53-0-41 (Archival box - standard 11-45)
    - Miscellaneous Metal (40-CB-13), 1977 - 1979; F-11-1-53-0-42 (Archival box - standard 11-45)
    - Supply and Install Precast Concrete (40-CB-14), 1978 - 1979; F-11-1-53-0-43 (Archival box - standard 11-45)
    - Toilet Partitions (40-CB-15), 1977 - 1979; F-11-1-53-0-44 (Archival box - standard 11-45)
    - Masonry (40-CB-16), 1977 - 1978; F-11-1-53-0-45 (Archival box - standard 11-45)
    - Folding Partitions (40-CB-17), 1977 - 1978; F-11-1-53-0-46 (Archival box - standard 11-45)
    - Rough Carpentry Part A (40-CB-18), 1977 - 1979; F-11-1-53-0-47 (Archival box - standard 11-46)
    - Rough Carpentry Part B (40-CB-18), 1977 - 1979; F-11-1-53-0-48 (Archival box - standard 11-46)
    - Finish Carpentry (40-CB-19), 1979; F-11-1-53-0-49 (Archival box - standard 11-46)
    - Overhead Doors (40-CB-20), 1977 - 1978; F-11-1-53-0-50 (Archival box - standard 11-46)
    - Mill Work Part A (40-CB-21), 1977 - 1979; F-11-1-53-0-51 (Archival box - standard 11-46)
    - Mill Work Part B (40-CB-21), 1977 - 1979; F-11-1-53-0-52 (Archival box - standard 11-46)
    - Drywall and Ceiling (40-CB-22), 1977 - 1979; F-11-1-53-0-53 (Archival box - standard 11-46)
    - Ceramic Tile (40-CB-23), 1978 - 1979; F-11-1-53-0-54 (Archival box - standard 11-47)
    - Resilient Flooring (40-CB-25), 1978 - 1979; F-11-1-53-0-55 (Archival box - standard 11-47)
    - Landscaping (40-CB-31), 1978 - 1979; F-11-1-53-0-56 (Archival box - standard 11-47)
    - Sidewalks and Court Yard (40-CB-32), 1977 - 1979; F-11-1-53-0-57 (Archival box - standard 11-47)
    - General Requirements (40-CB-35), 1976 - 1979; F-11-1-53-0-58 (Archival box - standard 11-47)
    - Hardwood Gym Floor (40-CB-36), 1978 - 1979; F-11-1-53-0-59 (Archival box - standard 11-47)
    - Air and Water Balancing (40-CB-37), 1978; F-11-1-53-0-60 (Archival box - standard 11-47)
  - Women's locker room renovations, 1977 - 1979; F-11-1-54; 9 cm of textual records
    - Women's Locker Room Renovations - General (49-01), 1978; F-11-1-54-0-1 (Archival box - standard 11-51)
    - Client/Architect Agreement (49-02), 1978; F-11-1-54-0-2 (Archival box - standard 11-51)
    - Cost Estimates (49-03), 1978; F-11-1-54-0-3 (Archival box - standard 11-51)
    - Capital Expenditures (49-04), 1978; F-11-1-54-0-4 (Archival box - standard 11-51)
    - Progress Certificates (49-04-01), 1978 - 1979; F-11-1-54-0-5 (Archival box - standard 11-51)
    - Payments to Architects (49-04-02), 1978; F-11-1-54-0-6 (Archival box - standard 11-51)
    - Miscellaneous Expenditures (49-04-04), 1978; F-11-1-54-0-7 (Archival box - standard 11-51)
    - Change Order Correspondence (49-05), 1978; F-11-1-54-0-8 (Archival box - standard 11-51)
    - Change Orders (49-05-01), 1978 - 1979; F-11-1-54-0-9 (Archival box - standard 11-51)
    - Design Changes (49-05-02), 1978; F-11-1-54-0-10 (Archival box - standard 11-51)
    - Inspections and Testing (49-06), 1978; F-11-1-54-0-11 (Archival box - standard 11-51)
    - Warranties and Guarantees (49-07), 1978; F-11-1-54-0-12 (Archival box - standard 11-51)
    - Fees (49-08), 1978; F-11-1-54-0-13 (Archival box - standard 11-51)
    - Deficiencies (49-09), 1978; F-11-1-54-0-14 (Archival box - standard 11-51)
    - Tenders Received (49-10), 1977 - 1978; F-11-1-54-0-15 (Archival box - standard 11-51)
    - Shop Drawings (49-11), 1978; F-11-1-54-0-16 (Archival box - standard 11-51)
    - Contractor's Liability (49-12), 1978; F-11-1-54-0-17 (Archival box - standard 11-51)
    - Building Contract (49-13), 1978; F-11-1-54-0-18 (Archival box - standard 11-51)
  - Classroom and office complex, 1977 - 1978; F-11-1-55; 3 cm of textual records
    - General (51-01), 1977 - 1978; F-11-1-55-0-1 (Archival box - standard 11-55)
    - Equipment lists and layouts (51-05), 1978; F-11-1-55-0-2 (Archival box - standard 11-55)
  - Faculty of Education (IMS structures), 1975 - 1979; F-11-1-56; 2 cm of textual records
    Faculty of Education
    - Faculty of Education - General (58-01), 1975 - 1978; F-11-1-56-0-1 (Archival box - standard 11-58)
    - Centre for the Arts Renovations (58-02), 1978 - 1979; F-11-1-56-0-2 (Archival box - standard 11-58)
  - Classroom block - Images Theatre, 1973 - 1978; F-11-1-57; 1 cm of textual records
    - Classroom block - Images Theatre (60-01), 1973 - 1978; F-11-1-57-0-1 (Archival box - standard 11-58)
  - Greenhouses, 1969 - 1979; F-11-1-58; 2 cm of textual records
    Department of Biological Sciences
    - Greenhouses - general (68-01), 1977 - 1979; F-11-1-58-0-1 (Archival box - standard 11-58)
    - Greenhouses - general (44-01?), 1969 - 1974; F-11-1-58-0-2 (Archival box - standard 11-58)
  - Animal care, 1972 - 1978; F-11-1-59; 11 cm of textual records
    - Animal Care Facilities - General (44-01), 1972 - 1978; F-11-1-59-0-1 (Archival box - standard 11-48)
    - Fees (44-02), 1975 - 1977; F-11-1-59-0-2 (Archival box - standard 11-48)
    - Schematics (44-04), 1977; F-11-1-59-0-3 (Archival box - standard 11-48)
    - Site Surveys (44-05), 1976; F-11-1-59-0-4 (Archival box - standard 11-48)
    - Working Drawings (44-06), 1977; F-11-1-59-0-5 (Archival box - standard 11-48)
    - Site Work Contracts (44-08), 1976; F-11-1-59-0-6 (Archival box - standard 11-48)
    - Progress Certificates (44-09), 1975 - 1977; F-11-1-59-0-7 (Archival box - standard 11-48)
    - Plans and Specs (44-10), 1975 - 1977; F-11-1-59-0-8 (Archival box - standard 11-48)
    - Equipment Lists and Layouts (44-11), 1977 - 1978; F-11-1-59-0-9 (Archival box - standard 11-49)
    - Animal Care - Change Orders (44-12), 1977; F-11-1-59-0-10 (Archival box - standard 11-49)
    - Design Changes (44-13), 1976; F-11-1-59-0-11 (Archival box - standard 11-49)
    - Minutes of Site Meetings (44-16), 1976; F-11-1-59-0-12 (Archival box - standard 11-49)
    - Mechanical Systems (44-17), 1978; F-11-1-59-0-13 (Archival box - standard 11-49)
    - Electrical Systems (44-18), 1975 - 1977; F-11-1-59-0-14 (Archival box - standard 11-49)
    - Inspections and Testing (44-19), 1976 - 1977; F-11-1-59-0-15 (Archival box - standard 11-49)
    - Hardware (44-20), 1975; F-11-1-59-0-16 (Archival box - standard 11-49)
    - Emergency Power (44-21), 1976; F-11-1-59-0-17 (Archival box - standard 11-49)
    - Substantial Completion (44-22), 1977; F-11-1-59-0-18 (Archival box - standard 11-49)
    - Deficiencies (44-23), 1977 - 1978; F-11-1-59-0-19 (Archival box - standard 11-49)
    - Outdoor Pens (44-24), 1977 - 1978; F-11-1-59-0-20 (Archival box - standard 11-49)
    - Alterations (44-25), 1978; F-11-1-59-0-21 (Archival box - standard 11-49)
- Legal cases, 1963 - 1980; F-11-2; 1.12 m of textual records
  Series consists of records relating to two cases of litigation in which Facilities Management was involved. It includes correspondence, engineering reports, pleadings and legal releases, specification books, and testimony and supporting documents.
  Some file titles were supplied and loose documents grouped by subject or function by the archivist.
  Access to records in this series is restricted in accordance with Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy legislation. Consult the unit list and the archivist for further information.
  - Mall roof litigation, 1963 - 1975; F-11-2-1; 74 cm of textual records
    Massey, Geoffrey; Erickson, Arthur
    - Insurance adjusters and university solicitors (38-06-22), 1969 - 1971; F-11-2-1-0-1 (Archival box - standard 11-63)
    - Shrum Liddle and Hebenton (38-06-22), 1967 - 1971; F-11-2-1-0-2 (Archival box - standard 11-63)
    - Breakage Patterns (38-06-26), 1969; F-11-2-1-0-3 (Archival box - standard 11-63)
    - Erickson-Massey Claim (38-06-32), 1965 - 1971; F-11-2-1-0-4 (Archival box - standard 11-63)
    - Architects - Extra Pleadings, F-11-2-1-0-5 (Archival box - standard 11-63)
    - Correspondence Between Clients and Architects, 1967; F-11-2-1-0-6 (Archival box - standard 11-63)
    - Erickson-Massey - Mall Roof Litigation, 1971 - 1973; F-11-2-1-0-7 (Archival box - standard 11-63)
    - Insurance - Mall Roof, 1968 - 1971; F-11-2-1-0-8 (Archival box - standard 11-63)
    - Insurance Claim - Mall Roof, 1971 - 1972; F-11-2-1-0-9 (Archival box - standard 11-63)
    - Laszlo George [Engineer], 1973; F-11-2-1-0-10 (Archival box - standard 11-63)
    - Spratt Report, 1965 - 1969; F-11-2-1-0-11 (Archival box - standard 11-63)
    - Mall Roof - Campus Development (20-20-4), 1965 - 1966; F-11-2-1-0-12 (Archival box - standard 11-64)
    - Mall Roof - Buildings (20-020-4A), 1964 - 1967; F-11-2-1-0-13 (Archival box - standard 11-64)
    - Mall Roof - Contracts Change Orders Progress Certificates (20-030-4A), 1965; F-11-2-1-0-14 (Archival box - standard 11-64)
    - Swan - Wooster Investigation (38-06-04), 1969; F-11-2-1-0-15 (Archival box - standard 11-64)
    - J. Lindsay and Associates (38-06-06), 1969; F-11-2-1-0-16 (Archival box - standard 11-64)
    - Northwest Report (38-06-08), 1969 - 1970; F-11-2-1-0-17 (Archival box - standard 11-64)
    - Climatological Station Report (38-06-10), 1965; F-11-2-1-0-18 (Archival box - standard 11-64)
    - Specs (38-06-12), 1969; F-11-2-1-0-19 (Archival box - standard 11-64)
    - Snow Loading (38-06-14), 1965 - 1972; F-11-2-1-0-20 (Archival box - standard 11-64)
    - Replacing Glass (Reglazing) (38-06-16), 1965 - 1969; F-11-2-1-0-21 (Archival box - standard 11-64)
    - Tenders (38-06-28), 1969 - 1970; F-11-2-1-0-22 (Archival box - standard 11-64)
    - Contract (38-06-30), F-11-2-1-0-23 (Archival box - standard 11-64)
    - Pleadings and Releases Part A, 1971 - 1975; F-11-2-1-0-24 (Archival box - standard 11-65)
    - Pleadings and Releases Part A, 1971 - 1975; F-11-2-1-0-25 (Archival box - standard 11-65)
    - Examination for Discovery - Arthur Erickson, 1973; F-11-2-1-0-26 (Archival box - standard 11-65)
    - Examination for Discovery - Geoffrey Massey, 1973; F-11-2-1-0-27 (Archival box - standard 11-65)
    - Examination for Discovery - John Kariotis, 1975; F-11-2-1-0-28 (Archival box - standard 11-65)
    - Examination for Discovery - Jeffrey Lindsay, 1975; F-11-2-1-0-29 (Archival box - standard 11-66)
    - Examination for Discovery - Arthur Orr, 1975; F-11-2-1-0-30 (Archival box - standard 11-66)
    - Supporting Documents (Indexed), 1963 - 1972; F-11-2-1-0-31 (Archival box - standard 11-66)
    - Examination for Discovery - William De Vries, 1975; F-11-2-1-0-32 (Archival box - standard 11-66)
    - Supporting Documents (Indexed), Part A, 1963 - 1972; F-11-2-1-0-33 (Archival box - standard 11-66)
    - Supporting Documents (Indexed), Part B, 1963 - 1972; F-11-2-1-0-34 (Archival box - standard 11-66)
    - Supporting Documents (Chronological), Part C, 1963 - 1968; F-11-2-1-0-35 (Archival box - standard 11-67)
    - Miscellaneous Legal Notes, 1975; F-11-2-1-0-36 (Archival box - standard 11-67)
    - Miscellaneous Papers, 1968 - 1975; F-11-2-1-0-37 (Archival box - standard 11-67)
    - Materials Testing, Part A, 1965 - 1967; F-11-2-1-0-38 (Archival box - standard 11-67)
    - Materials Testing, Part B, 1965 - 1967; F-11-2-1-0-39 (Archival box - standard 11-67)
    - Reports, 1965 - 1969; F-11-2-1-0-40 (Archival box - standard 11-67)
    - Spec Books, 1965; F-11-2-1-0-41 (Archival box - standard 11-67)
    - Supporting Documents (Chronological), Part A, 1963 - 1972; F-11-2-1-0-42 (Archival box - standard 11-68)
    - Supporting Documents (Chronological), Part B, 1963 - 1972; F-11-2-1-0-43 (Archival box - standard 11-68)
    - Supporting Documents (Chronological), Part A, 1963 - 1968; F-11-2-1-0-44 (Archival box - standard 11-68)
    - Supporting Documents (Chronological), Part B, 1963 - 1968; F-11-2-1-0-45 (Archival box - standard 11-68)
  - Prossegger case, 1977 - 1980; F-11-2-2; 38 cm of textual records
    Fred Prosegger; Muir, Charles
    - Documents in Evidence, Part A, 1977 - 1978; F-11-2-2-0-1 (Archival box - standard 11-69)
    - Documents in Evidence, Part B, 1977 - 1978; F-11-2-2-0-2 (Archival box - standard 11-69)
    - Documents in Evidence, Part C, 1977 - 1978; F-11-2-2-0-3 (Archival box - standard 11-69)
    - Correspondence, Part A, 1977 - 1978; F-11-2-2-0-4 (Archival box - standard 11-69)
    - Correspondence, Part B, 1977 - 1978; F-11-2-2-0-5 (Archival box - standard 11-69)
    - Variation Orders, Work Orders, Progress Claims, 1977 - 1978; F-11-2-2-0-6 (Archival box - standard 11-69)
    - Examination for Discovery - Fred Prossegger, 1980; F-11-2-2-0-7 (Archival box - standard 11-70)
    - Examination for Discovery - Fred Prossegger, 1980; F-11-2-2-0-8 (Archival box - standard 11-70)
    - Examination for Discovery - Fred Prossegger, 1980; F-11-2-2-0-9 (Archival box - standard 11-70)
    - Examination for Discovery - Fred Prossegger, 1980; F-11-2-2-0-10 (Archival box - standard 11-70)
    - Examination for Discovery - Fred Prossegger, 1980; F-11-2-2-0-11 (Archival box - standard 11-70)
    - Examination for Discovery - Fred Prossegger, 1980; F-11-2-2-0-12 (Archival box - standard 11-70)
    - Examination for Discovery - Fred Prossegger, 1980; F-11-2-2-0-13 (Archival box - standard 11-70)
    - Examination for Discovery - Fred Prossegger, 1980; F-11-2-2-0-14 (Archival box - standard 11-70)
    - Examination for Discovery - Fred Prossegger, 1980; F-11-2-2-0-15 (Archival box - standard 11-70)
    - Examination for Discovery - Charles Muir, 1980; F-11-2-2-0-16 (Archival box - standard 11-71)
    - Examination for Discovery - Charles Muir, 1980; F-11-2-2-0-17 (Archival box - standard 11-71)
    - Examination for Discovery - Charles Muir, 1980; F-11-2-2-0-18 (Archival box - standard 11-71)
    - Examination for Discovery - Charles Muir, 1980; F-11-2-2-0-19 (Archival box - standard 11-71)
    - Examination for Discovery - Charles Muir, 1980; F-11-2-2-0-20 (Archival box - standard 11-71)
    - Examination for Discovery - Charles Muir, 1980; F-11-2-2-0-21 (Archival box - standard 11-71)
    - Examination for Discovery - Charles Muir, 1980; F-11-2-2-0-22 (Archival box - standard 11-71)
    - Examination for Discovery - Charles Muir, 1980; F-11-2-2-0-23 (Archival box - standard 11-71)
    - Examination for Discovery - Charles Muir, 1980; F-11-2-2-0-24 (Archival box - standard 11-71)
- Departmental files, 1960 - 2003; F-11-3; 3 m of textual records